Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The Black Bulls have finally made it to the Underwater Temple. However, when they arrived...
You came to my temple to seek the magic stone, didn't you? If you want it, you'll have to play a game with me first!
A mysterious old man, the High Priest, and his nine temple mages were waiting for them.
The High Priest separated the Black Bulls, telling them they must fight the mages nine on nine if they want to leave with the magic stone.
The team that wipes out all of their opponents, or the one with the most players left standing when the game concludes, will be the winner!
Oh yeah! I'm so there! This is gonna be a total bloodbath!
Hold on. Did he say it was going to be a nine on nine battle? But there should be ten of us.
Alright! I got it! Now let's go! I'm ready!
How interesting. I'm not sensing so much as a scrap of magic coming from you. Too bad. Looks like I got a dud.
You think I'm a dud, huh? Just try me and find out!
Bye!
Hide your ears!
Bye yeah yeah
Just move it back
Backに抱きしめ
合わせしましょう上
Just move it back
光灯して
真っ暗な音ろへ
Just move it back
La la la la la...
Wow!
Just move it back
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
You don't mind, I'll keep the books coming back
I'm afraid that won't work, you're too strong
I've been looking forward to this
And so have all the good people who are watching from outside
Can't have the fun end too quickly, now can we?
Well, hell, looks like you've got a good eye for fighting skill, old man
This geezer knows a thing or two
Oh, looks like some of the competitors have crossed paths
Those idiots better not lose or I'll kill them
I'm so cold, I'm gonna make that crazy old bastard pay
That's priceless, fire magic in an underwater temple
This should be very entertaining
So small and fragile looking
I'll almost feel ashamed when I tear you apart
Oh, are you the one I get to fight?
I've heard of you people, you're the Black Bulls
They say you're the weakest of all the Magic Knight squads
Marie is waiting, let's just get this over with
So you know, waving around that rusty old sword is a waste of your time
I can dodge any attack you throw at me with my mollusk magic
My toes are practically tingling
Out of curiosity, Captain, how are those mages of yours ranked?
They're all still at the junior level
I'm surprised you know about ranks living down here
All my temple mages are more powerful than intermediate class magic knights
And they're out there fighting a bunch of juniors?
Your poor schmucks don't stand a chance in this battle
Wow, that's bad
Guess we're in trouble
Unless those poor schmucks are actually stronger than their ranks suggest
They're losing! That's impossible!
It's gonna take more than a few drops of water to scare me off
I say we turn this little battle into a fish fry
I guess that must have been one of their weaker guys
How boring, wonder where the tough ones are
There, now that's done, we can move on to much more important things
Like getting back to Marie
I don't understand
My mollusk magic should be able to deflect any kind of physical attack
That stuff's not gonna work on me! This is an anti-magic sword!
Who's up next?
Yeah, beat the crap out of those fish!
Idiots! Letting them get the drop on you!
Hey, how about we bet on which team's gonna win this game of yours?
I'm putting 10,000 Yule on the bulls
Please! This is just the beginning
The mages who are left won't go down as easily as those others
In fact, my three great mages rival senior ranked magic knights in terms of power
Don't see me
Phew, that was a close one
I have no desire to fight someone that scary looking
I've been trying to get back to where this all started
But I can't seem to for some reason
Looks like for now I can only use magic to get to places that I can see
Oh yes, there's one thing I neglected to tell you
Until the game is over, you won't be able to leave!
Hey! Are you watching me, old man?
Federal, quit hiding and fight already, you wuss
Wait, you're watching too yummy? But how?
Don't tell me you're with the crazy priest
We're having a feast with your fights as the entertainment
What? If you're with him, can't you get him to call off this game? It's brutal!
Yeah, the brutal part's what makes it fun
I couldn't have said it better
Great, they're buddies now?
You know, this'll be a lot less fun if your knights are just gonna run away
Yeah, we gotta make them fight
Well, it's time for some nuisance magic
Game magic, master time!
Look at him go! I should give him a few more to play with
Listen up, geezer
That didn't look deadly enough
Can you whip up something more like this?
Just to clarify, you're on their side, aren't you?
Nice drawing, though
Now, let's see how the rest of those little idiots are holding up
Gray's turned into a crab and scuttled off somewhere
Gonna kill them around later
Oh, looks like Charmy's fighting
Wow, I've never seen anything like this before
Yes, the underwater temple's denizens are truly yummy!
Show our jumps!
Invite a northern sheep for you so magnificent
You're out of control for a long time ago
For a strong magic reason or not
Aw, if only my prince of provisions were here to savor this feast with me
That's it!
I hereby claim this ecosystem in the name of Charmy!
And I'm gonna keep eating till it's empty!
Ha ha ha ha!
What, uh...
Is she doing exactly?
Oh, yeah
Here we go
And it's all for me
Found you!
Ha ha ha ha!
Oh, look at what a cutie you are
Too bad I'm gonna have to squash you
Ha ha ha!
Is that right?
Well, right now I'm full of mana from all those tasty little sea creatures I ate
You want to see if you'll manage any better against my teeth than they did?
Then let's dance!
Awwww!
Song Magic, Mother Lullaby
Wow, I feel really good all of a sudden
No way, I can hear more
That's one down.
Oh, I should have mentioned that sleeping counts as a knockout.
Well, what do you think now that you've seen one of my great mages in action?
When we get back, she's on short rations for a week.
That was fun. Maybe I'll run into my new friends next.
Nice. My clothes are finally dry after that dowsing earlier.
I wonder who my next victim's gonna be.
Huh? Well, it looks like you're still alive and kicking, Lightning Boy.
Yep. And I knocked out a temple mage.
I headed this way because I thought I was picking up on something pretty strong.
And oh goody, it looks like I was right.
Hell yeah. Now we just gotta decide which one of us are gonna-
Hey, look! No fear! Come back here, you jerk!
Ha ha ha ha! But comfort serve! Sorry!
Lightning magic! Thunderbolt Destruction!
Water creation magic! See God, see him!
He's tough. Lightning and water should be a good match, too.
Well, well. Aren't you a spunky little fella?
Ha ha ha!
Ready.
Yaargh! Gotcha slimy!
Hiya!
Huff.
That key. Someon's there.
The
Aww, come on, Grandpa. Can't you save the nuisance spells for the other team?
Well, whatever. It was a good warm-up, I guess.
He beat that huge thing?
Who is he?
Huh?
Oh, hey there. You're Asta, aren't you?
Uh, yeah, that's me.
I've heard about you. You wield a strange sword that cancels out magic.
Sure, that's right.
Wait, heard what from who?
Never mind that. Check out this dance.
But we're supposed to be fighting!
Still, that's a pretty awesome dance!
How do you think it'd go over on land?
They would love it!
I'm Kioto. My dream is to captivate the entire kingdom with my dancing!
Now he's talking about his dreams?
Except, while we underwater temple folk can go to the kingdom's beaches if we want, we're not allowed to visit any of the cities.
But that could change soon!
Because if I win this fight, then Grandpa...
Oh, yeah, the high priest is my grandfather, by the way.
Anyhow, he said he'll use his authority to let me go ashore!
Yes! I'm going to make it big as a star dancer!
That's a huge dream, alright!
Hey, wait.
Where have I heard something like that before?
So I must apologize!
But for the sake of my dream, you must lose this fight!
So fast!
Yeah, well, you're not the only one with a dream!
Huh?
That's right.
I want to become the strongest mage, the Wizard King, the protector of the kingdom!
So sorry.
But for the sake of my dream, I'm going to take you down!
All right.
We'll both put our dreams on the line, and fight without holding anything back!
I wouldn't have it any other way!
Great.
What am I supposed to do?
How can I fight when I haven't learned a single proper attack spell yet?
Awesome!
I finally found you!
Oh no, a temple mage!
Well, I suppose it's only fair to warn you I am royalty!
Fight at your own risk!
Now's your last chance to run!
How cute!
I'm so glad you came, Noelle!
Wait a sec, how do you know my name?
Oh, silly me!
I forgot about the whole mask thing!
Kohono!
I've been waiting for you!
Hiya!
You live here?
You're one of the temple mages we're supposed to fight.
Then why were you so eager to help me learn how to control my magic?
Yeah, about that.
I wasn't just practicing up by the beach,
I was also looking for people who wanted to come down and visit us.
When we have visitors, Grandpa, um,
the High Priest, always wants to play this game.
And if I win, then I get to go ashore,
which means that I can finally become an idol!
That's why?
So then, you were using me the whole time!
What?
No, I wasn't.
When I saw how hard you were trying,
I really did want to help you,
and I totally still want to be your friend, too.
But!
Now we're facing off against each other in this game,
and we have to fight fair and square!
But why?
You just said we were friends, didn't you?
Yep!
But real friends can fight for what's most important to them
and still be able to laugh with each other afterwards!
Song magic!
Mother Lullaby!
What's this spell?
It's making me...
Water creation magic!
Sea Dragon's Lair!
Oh, so you are ready to fight!
Song magic!
Destructive bait!
Oh, come on, Noelle!
You've got to use some attack spells, too!
I really didn't want to do this!
Wow!
That's just from releasing her magic power?
Jeez!
Really?
What the heck are you doing, Noelle?
There's no point attacking if you're just gonna miss!
You need to aim correctly if you want to beat me!
Shut up!
I still can't control my attacks, but you don't have to be such a jerk about it, okay?
Sure you can. What are you talking about? You're controlling your magic just fine.
You're unconsciously trying to avoid attacking me.
You don't want to hurt people.
Now that works out fine for me, but think about the reason that you're here.
Didn't you come because you wanted to see a dream fulfilled?
Well, that isn't going to happen unless you fight me and win.
Why did I come?
Because I want to help the others.
Fine, let's fight!
This guy's really strong, and the way he moves is crazy.
It's like his mind's not here, but off somewhere else.
His key's so hard to read!
Feels like he's scrambling my senses.
Is that his magic?
As I thought.
Against my real blades, your anti-magic sword is nothing more than a chunk of steel.
With my dance magic as an added bonus, you can't track my movements at all!
Ha ha! My grandson's pretty powerful, don't you think?
Nice swordsmanship, I'll give him that. But still...
Well, Asuka? Come on, aren't you ready to surrender yet?
Not good!
If he keeps this up, I'm in trouble!
It's like trying to grab water!
Wait a second.
Maybe strength's not what I need.
Water's shapeless, so grabbing it's impossible.
Stay calm.
I know!
Woo!
If I want to beat him, I have to be like water, too!
Monkey see, monkey do. Now that's amusing.
Ooh! Ah!
Watch what this monkey can do!
I may not have any magic!
Who cares?
I can just use my body to mimic it instead!
Ha ha! Without magic, there are limits to what you can do.
What? Oh yeah? Well, in that case...
This is where I push past my limits!
Impressive. How strong is this kid?
Ha ha ha ha! My guy's magic-sucking skill is even more powerful!
Huh?
Secretly setting a trap for a poor, defenseless woman like me.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
Now, now, you can't complain just because you got caught instead.
Seriously?
Vanessa's usually either too drunk or hungover to manage much of anything useful.
The bulls are killing it today.
Really should have bet more.
You said that your knights were junior-ranked mages.
There's certainly nothing junior about the chest on that woman.
Better get that magic stone ready, old man.
There's a real nasty group called the Eye of the Midnight Sun that's after it, too.
I can promise you that you're better off handing it over to us.
Ha! You're only saying that because my mages are making a comeback.
At this point, that kind of bluster makes you sound desperate, either.
I'm telling you, we'll win!
The tables will turn in no time once my top mages are able to show what they can do.
I'll have you know my son is the most powerful mage in the Underwater Temple.
This is fun!
You look like you're getting tired, though.
Wanna take a break?
Yeah, right.
I could keep going all day if I needed to.
But if you need a break, go ahead.
Sorry about this.
My old man sure does like his games, though.
Hold on a second.
That crazy old coot is your father?
He's got so much power.
Like a tidal wave.
No doubt about it.
This guy is the strongest one here.
I'll take you both on at once.
I'm not interested in tormenting you any further.
The least I can do for you is end this quickly.
Water creation magic, Poseidon's Hammer!
You're not going to be ending anything.
Yeah, I'm nowhere near done playing with you!
Why is everything shaking?
That's not part of the game!
What's going on here?
Well, it looks like you folks are having quite a get-together.
How about you guys let me in the mix?
Just lately, I've been crying for hours, baby.
I wish you were here.
How about you guys let me in the up front?
Hi.
離れ離れでも
繋がるBelieve in you
いつもそばに
感じているから
Closer to me
And I'll go before you
君に call
You know you're not alone
Cause we are perfect as for
離れ離れでも
繋がるBelieve in you
いつもそばに
私がいるから
Closer to me
And I'll go before you
君に call
Let me in the mix
Well it looks like you folks
Are having quite a get together
How about
You guys let me in the mix
I don't understand
Did I get the wrong place or something
Wanna try?
Wanna try some?
I am kinda hungry
Since I'm here anyway
I might as well get in the mix
Thanks
What are you waiting for?
Get mixing
Go on
Like I always say
Those who do not work shall not numb
Mix, mix
It's not about sheer strength
Cooking takes knowledge, skill and patience
Right
I see now
Thank you
And so Vetto
His eyes opened to the joy of cooking
Left without retrieving the magic stone
And everyone lived happily ever after
I mean it could happen right?
No way
I Vetto of the third eye
Will recover the magic stone
For the eye of the midnight sun
Black Clover page 44
The pointlessly direct fireball
And the wild lightning
My beast magic will crush everything